Okay, it's two o'clock.  The bell at Sunnyside has rung,
好了，到了下午二时了  阳光日间托儿中心的下课钟声应该已经响了
so Bonnie is officially  on her winter break.
所以宝妮的寒假正式开始
-Soon she'll be flying off to...  -Hay-way-I.
- 她将快要飞到...  - 哈-威-衣
It's Hawaii, Buzz.  Does everybody have a vacation plan?
巴斯，是夏威夷  有没有人已计划怎样渡假？
Rex and I have been working on  our massively multiplayer,
抱抱龙和我正在玩我们的  重型多人...
online, role-playing game profiles.
线上角色扮演游戏
The Rexing Ball!
超级抱抱龙！
That's me !  Can you make my arms bigger?
那就是我  你可以把我的手臂弄大一点？
Oh, yeah. Enhancing.
没问题，放大中...
Oh, yes!
棒极了！
-Potato Head, you in?  -Sorry, fellas. He's all mine.
- 薯蛋头先生，一起玩吗？  - 对不起，他是拥于我的
We're going to have a fun-filled week,  just the two of us.
我们二人将有一个充满乐趣的一周
Deal me in.
我也玩
Thank you all  for coming to the audition.
多谢各位来参与试镜
Number one, action.
一号，开始
Dreadful. Next.
十分可怕！  下一位...
Horrifying. Next.
真是糟透！  下一位...
Brilliant!
太好了！
Bonnie's coming !
宝妮快要来到
Vacation to Hawaii ! Going on vacation !
夏威夷渡假！  去夏威夷渡假！
-Vacation, vacation.  -Bonnie !
- 去渡假了...  - 宝妮
Coming, Mom !
妈，来了
Bye, toys.
玩具们，再见
-All right, folks, let the relaxing begin.  -Hooray!
- 好了各位，是放松的时间了  - 万岁
Ready to lose at checkers, Slink?
准备好输掉这盘棋局了吗，弹弓狗？
When pigs fly.
绝不可能
Actually, I had an uncle  who was a pilot.
事实上，我有一个叔叔  他是一个飞机师
-Really?  -No, not really.
- 真的？  - 不，其实是假的
Here's your bag, Barbie.
Barbie，你的手袋
-You can put my luggage right here.  -Ken, this is so exciting !
- 你可以直接把我的行李放左这里  - Ken，这真是令人兴奋
Picture ! Say "sunscreen."
拍照吧！  说“夏威夷﹣”
-Sunscreen.  -Perfect.
- 夏威夷﹣  - 非常好
-Ka-click.  -Barbie? Ken?
- 咔嚓  - Barbie？Ken？
Woody? Hey!
胡迪？ 嘿！
You guys are in Hawaii, too! Groovy.
你们都在夏威夷吗？  太好了
We stowed away  in Bonnie's backpack.
我们偷偷藏在宝妮的背包内
How did you guys get here?
你们是怎样来的？
Ken, this is Bonnie's bedroom.
Ken，这是宝妮的睡房
What?
什么？
-And there she goes.  -No. No, no. No, no.
- 而且她已经走了  - 噢，不..
No!
不...
Bonnie !
宝妮
You can't go.  Not without the backpack.
你不能走的  你不能不带背包的
Let me get this straight.
我就有话直说吧
You thought Bonnie would take  her school backpack on vacation?
你认为宝妮会带她的学校背包去渡假吗？
-Oh, boy.  -Hawaii !
-Oh, boy.  - 夏威夷！
-You have to take us to Hawaii !  -Sorry, sir. I just zip and unzip.
- 你带我们到夏威夷吧  - 对不起，我只懂把拉链拉开和关上
-I don't actually fly.  -Hey?
- 我不懂飞的  - 嘿？
Ken?
Ken？
I... I'll be right back.
我...马上回来
He's been planning this vacation  for months.
他为了此渡假已计划了数个月了
Wow. That's a lot of numbering.
哇，上面有许多数目字呢
Did he do that all by himself?
这全都是他做的吗？
Ken doesn't know I know,  but this is where he planned
Ken并不知我知道他的计划  其实他计划在那里...
to have our very first kiss.
来给我一个初吻
You haven't kissed yet?
你们还没有亲吻过？
It would have been  the perfect vacation.
这本是一个完美的假期
-Ken, could you please come out here?  -No!
- Ken，你可以出一出来吗？  - 不！
I can't decide if this handbag  matches my shoes.
我不知这手袋与我的鞋子是否相配
Well, are you wearing the pumps  or the espadrilles?
那么，你是穿平底鞋还是高跟鞋？
Welcome to paradise.
欢迎来到天堂
We've got the vacation of your dreams  all planned out for you !
我们为你们准备了你们的梦想假期
Welcome to the Bonnielikeoke Motel.
欢迎来到宝妮都钟意嚟酒店
I thought we were staying in a resort.
还以为是住渡假村酒店...
-Welcome to the Bonnielikeoke Resort.  -This is great!
- 欢迎来到宝妮都钟意嚟渡假村酒店  - 太棒了！
"Immerse yourself  in a whole new world
“让你置身全新世界的...
"when you go deep sea diving ! "
深海潜游”
I've got the perfect outfit!
我有一套完美的服装
Whoa, look at that.
哇，看看那个
Beautiful.
十分美丽
Watch this.
看看这个
Shark Week.
鲨鱼特辑
Nice.
非常好
Next up, a guided nature hike.
接下来是大自然导赏游
There's the official Hawaiian state bird,  the Nene.
这是代表夏威夷的雀鸟  叻叻鸟
-Nay-nay.  -Ka-click.
- 叻叻  - 咔嚓
And the state fish,  the humuhumunukunukuapua'a.
这就这个州的代表鱼  游吓游吓走吓走吓行吓行吓飞吓飞吓鱼
-Ka-click.  -And a pineapple.
- 咔嚓  - 还有个菠萝
-How you doing?  -Ka-click.
- 你究竟在做什么？  - 咔嚓
You're not wearing any pants.
你没有穿裤子
Ride like the wind, Bullseye !
红心，要跑得像风一般！
Ride like the wind, Buttercup!
牛油，要跑得像风一般
Okay! Get off me.
好了！快下来了！
You're really rippin' those curls, Ken.
Ken，你真的在征服这些浪呢
Watch me hang ten, Babs.
看我表演花式吧
Gin.
胜利
I'm okay.
我还好
Dinner is served.
晚餐经已送上
I should've seen this coming.
我早已预见这
The entertainment  will start in just a moment.
表演快将开始
Hey, Buzz!
嘿，巴斯
Hello ladies and gentlemen.
女士们，先生们
Barbie, we're almost ready for  the place where you have your first...
Barbie，地方已准备好让你们初...
Thanks, but I got this one covered.
谢了，不过我已安排好这个了
-Hey, Ken, come with me for a minute.  -Okay.
- Ken，跟我来  - 好吧
Woody, the beach is all set.
胡迪，沙滩已准备好
We removed the poop  from the kitty litter.
〔西班牙语〕
Spanish is so beautiful !
西班牙语真是美丽
Hey, everybody, look out the window.
各位  看看外面吧
What are they doing out there?
他们在外面做什么？
It's got to be a bazillion degrees below.
外面温度一定是零下过亿度
Good thing they wore  the 1982 Winter Weekend Collection.
还好他们都穿了  1982年的冬季系列
Looks like she does  have this one covered.
看来她真的安排好了
Ka-click.
咔嚓
-How romantic!  -Yeah. Until they fall off the deck.
- 多么的浪漫  - 是的，如果他们没有跌下来的话
I'll get the shovel.
我去拿铁铲
Best vacation ever.
最美好的假期
Yeah.
对